{"text": "Alexandros is best known today for the Venus de Milo ( Aphrodite of Milos ) at the Louvre Museum in Paris , France .", "tokens": ["Alexandros", "is", "best", "known", "today", "for", "the", "Venus", "de", "Milo", "(", "Aphrodite", "of", "Milos", ")", "at", "the", "Louvre", "Museum", "in", "Paris", ",", "France", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0], "text": "Alexandros"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [7, 8, 9], "text": "Venus de Milo"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Aphrodite of Milos"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Louvre Museum"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [20], "text": "Paris"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "France"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "art", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Alexandros", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Venus de Milo", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Aphrodite of Milos", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Louvre Museum", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Paris", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "France", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The character will be portrayed by Sharon Duncan-Brewster in the 2021 Denis Villeneuve film , `` Dune `` .", "tokens": ["The", "character", "will", "be", "portrayed", "by", "Sharon", "Duncan-Brewster", "in", "the", "2021", "Denis", "Villeneuve", "film", ",", "``", "Dune", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11, 12], "text": "Denis Villeneuve"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [16], "text": "Dune"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Denis Villeneuve", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dune", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Every five years the ARBA publishes a detailed guide entitled `` Standard of Perfection `` .", "tokens": ["Every", "five", "years", "the", "ARBA", "publishes", "a", "detailed", "guide", "entitled", "``", "Standard", "of", "Perfection", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [4], "text": "ARBA"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Standard of Perfection"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "ARBA", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Standard of Perfection", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "By 1918 the NZAOC had grown to include a New Zealand Ordnance Corps Section , consisting of 3 Officer and 53 ORs under the control of the NZEF Administrative Headquarters in London , with the New Zealand Ordnance Base Depot at Farringdon Street , London .", "tokens": ["By", "1918", "the", "NZAOC", "had", "grown", "to", "include", "a", "New", "Zealand", "Ordnance", "Corps", "Section", ",", "consisting", "of", "3", "Officer", "and", "53", "ORs", "under", "the", "control", "of", "the", "NZEF", "Administrative", "Headquarters", "in", "London", ",", "with", "the", "New", "Zealand", "Ordnance", "Base", "Depot", "at", "Farringdon", "Street", ",", "London", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3], "text": "NZAOC"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [9, 10, 11, 12, 13], "text": "New Zealand Ordnance Corps Section"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [27], "text": "NZEF"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [31], "text": "London"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [35, 36, 37, 38, 39], "text": "New Zealand Ordnance Base Depot"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [41, 42], "text": "Farringdon Street"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [44], "text": "London"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "NZAOC", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "New Zealand Ordnance Corps Section", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NZEF", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "New Zealand Ordnance Base Depot", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Farringdon Street", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "D at the University of Hawaii at Manoa .", "tokens": ["D", "at", "the", "University", "of", "Hawaii", "at", "Manoa", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4, 5], "text": "University of Hawaii"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [7], "text": "Manoa"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "University of Hawaii", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Manoa", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Until 1928 there were no official RFB groups in Bavaria .", "tokens": ["Until", "1928", "there", "were", "no", "official", "RFB", "groups", "in", "Bavaria", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [6], "text": "RFB"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [9], "text": "Bavaria"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "RFB", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bavaria", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He authored the JI bomb manual , used in the Bali bombing and the 2003 Marriott Hotel bombing .", "tokens": ["He", "authored", "the", "JI", "bomb", "manual", ",", "used", "in", "the", "Bali", "bombing", "and", "the", "2003", "Marriott", "Hotel", "bombing", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "JI bomb"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Bali bombing"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [15, 16, 17], "text": "Marriott Hotel bombing"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "JI bomb", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bali bombing", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Marriott Hotel bombing", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "All of these different groups took part in the Iranian revolution in 1979 .", "tokens": ["All", "of", "these", "different", "groups", "took", "part", "in", "the", "Iranian", "revolution", "in", "1979", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Iranian revolution"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Iranian revolution", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Furthermore , because the playoff format was also changed to ensure exclusive intradivisional play for the first two rounds of the 2021 Stanley Cup playoffs , any postseason rematch between Dallas and Tampa Bay will take place no later than the second round , making this series the first Stanley Cup Finals since 1967 Stanley Cup Finals ( which preceded the 1967 NHL expansion ) for which a rematch in the following year 's Finals will be impossible due to League realignment .", "tokens": ["Furthermore", ",", "because", "the", "playoff", "format", "was", "also", "changed", "to", "ensure", "exclusive", "intradivisional", "play", "for", "the", "first", "two", "rounds", "of", "the", "2021", "Stanley", "Cup", "playoffs", ",", "any", "postseason", "rematch", "between", "Dallas", "and", "Tampa", "Bay", "will", "take", "place", "no", "later", "than", "the", "second", "round", ",", "making", "this", "series", "the", "first", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "since", "1967", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "(", "which", "preceded", "the", "1967", "NHL", "expansion", ")", "for", "which", "a", "rematch", "in", "the", "following", "year", "'s", "Finals", "will", "be", "impossible", "due", "to", "League", "realignment", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [30], "text": "Dallas"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [32, 33], "text": "Tampa Bay"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [49, 50], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [54, 55], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [62], "text": "NHL"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dallas", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tampa Bay", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NHL", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Arthur perished on Glastonbury Tor in 1539 , hung , drawn and quartered alongside his master , Richard Whiting , the last Abbot of Glastonbury , during the dissolution of the monasteries .", "tokens": ["Arthur", "perished", "on", "Glastonbury", "Tor", "in", "1539", ",", "hung", ",", "drawn", "and", "quartered", "alongside", "his", "master", ",", "Richard", "Whiting", ",", "the", "last", "Abbot", "of", "Glastonbury", ",", "during", "the", "dissolution", "of", "the", "monasteries", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Arthur"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Glastonbury Tor"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Richard Whiting"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24], "text": "Glastonbury"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Arthur", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Glastonbury Tor", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Richard Whiting", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Glastonbury", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Herodotus , in his `` Histories `` , Book II , gives a detailed if selectively coloured and imaginative description of ancient Egypt .", "tokens": ["Herodotus", ",", "in", "his", "``", "Histories", "``", ",", "Book", "II", ",", "gives", "a", "detailed", "if", "selectively", "coloured", "and", "imaginative", "description", "of", "ancient", "Egypt", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Herodotus"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [5], "text": "Histories"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [8, 9], "text": "Book II"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "Egypt"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Herodotus", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Histories", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Book II", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Egypt", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "William 's successful invasion of England with a Dutch fleet and army led to his accession to the English throne as William III of England jointly with his wife Mary II of England , James ' daughter .", "tokens": ["William", "'s", "successful", "invasion", "of", "England", "with", "a", "Dutch", "fleet", "and", "army", "led", "to", "his", "accession", "to", "the", "English", "throne", "as", "William", "III", "of", "England", "jointly", "with", "his", "wife", "Mary", "II", "of", "England", ",", "James", "'", "daughter", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "William"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [5], "text": "England"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [8], "text": "Dutch"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18], "text": "English"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [21, 22], "text": "William III"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24], "text": "England"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [29, 30], "text": "Mary II"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [32], "text": "England"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [34], "text": "James"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "William", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dutch", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "English", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "William III", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mary II", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "James", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "1969 - The Renault 12 medium-sized saloon and estate range is launched , but it missed out on the European Car of the Year award , which goes to the Fiat 128 from Italy .", "tokens": ["1969", "-", "The", "Renault", "12", "medium-sized", "saloon", "and", "estate", "range", "is", "launched", ",", "but", "it", "missed", "out", "on", "the", "European", "Car", "of", "the", "Year", "award", ",", "which", "goes", "to", "the", "Fiat", "128", "from", "Italy", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Renault 12"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24], "text": "European Car of the Year award"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [30, 31], "text": "Fiat 128"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [33], "text": "Italy"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other", "product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Renault 12", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "European Car of the Year award", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Fiat 128", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Italy", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He watched the 1958 World Cup as a journalist and saw the Brazilian national football team 's football .", "tokens": ["He", "watched", "the", "1958", "World", "Cup", "as", "a", "journalist", "and", "saw", "the", "Brazilian", "national", "football", "team", "'s", "football", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "World Cup"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "Brazilian"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "World Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Brazilian", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Septic shock is a result of a systemic response to infection or multiple infectious causes .", "tokens": ["Septic", "shock", "is", "a", "result", "of", "a", "systemic", "response", "to", "infection", "or", "multiple", "infectious", "causes", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Septic shock"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Septic shock", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "CikA is a major factor in the input pathway and causes KaiC dependent cell elongation .", "tokens": ["CikA", "is", "a", "major", "factor", "in", "the", "input", "pathway", "and", "causes", "KaiC", "dependent", "cell", "elongation", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [0], "text": "CikA"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [11], "text": "KaiC"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "CikA", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "KaiC", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Gough Island was formally claimed in 1938 for Britain , during a visit by HMS `` Milford '' of the Royal Navy .", "tokens": ["Gough", "Island", "was", "formally", "claimed", "in", "1938", "for", "Britain", ",", "during", "a", "visit", "by", "HMS", "``", "Milford", "''", "of", "the", "Royal", "Navy", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Gough Island"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Britain"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [14, 15, 16, 17], "text": "HMS `` Milford ''"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [20, 21], "text": "Royal Navy"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Gough Island", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Britain", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "HMS `` Milford ''", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Royal Navy", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In Cochin , India , at the shore establishment HMS `` Chinkara '' ( home of the Landing Craft Storage , Section 21 ) , many such craft were towed out to the 10 fathom mark and sunk by various means from axe to 40mm Bofors gun fire .", "tokens": ["In", "Cochin", ",", "India", ",", "at", "the", "shore", "establishment", "HMS", "``", "Chinkara", "''", "(", "home", "of", "the", "Landing", "Craft", "Storage", ",", "Section", "21", ")", ",", "many", "such", "craft", "were", "towed", "out", "to", "the", "10", "fathom", "mark", "and", "sunk", "by", "various", "means", "from", "axe", "to", "40mm", "Bofors", "gun", "fire", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [1], "text": "Cochin"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [3], "text": "India"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [9, 10, 11, 12], "text": "HMS `` Chinkara ''"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [44, 45, 46], "text": "40mm Bofors gun"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Cochin", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "India", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "HMS `` Chinkara ''", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "40mm Bofors gun", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "After they see the picture of the Castle and try their hand at the games they might come here and try the real thing . ''", "tokens": ["After", "they", "see", "the", "picture", "of", "the", "Castle", "and", "try", "their", "hand", "at", "the", "games", "they", "might", "come", "here", "and", "try", "the", "real", "thing", ".", "''"], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The airline closed operations in 2005 .", "tokens": ["The", "airline", "closed", "operations", "in", "2005", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Friday 's by mid-2016 .", "tokens": ["Friday", "'s", "by", "mid-2016", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The Painted Desert Visitor Center , designed by modernist architect Richard Neutra , is part of the Painted Desert Community Complex Historic District listed on the National Register of Historic Places .", "tokens": ["The", "Painted", "Desert", "Visitor", "Center", ",", "designed", "by", "modernist", "architect", "Richard", "Neutra", ",", "is", "part", "of", "the", "Painted", "Desert", "Community", "Complex", "Historic", "District", "listed", "on", "the", "National", "Register", "of", "Historic", "Places", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [1, 2, 3, 4], "text": "Painted Desert Visitor Center"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Richard Neutra"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22], "text": "Painted Desert Community Complex Historic District"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Painted Desert Visitor Center", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Richard Neutra", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Painted Desert Community Complex Historic District", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 1654 the Congregazione dei Nobili put Picchiatti in charge of designing and building the Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi .", "tokens": ["In", "1654", "the", "Congregazione", "dei", "Nobili", "put", "Picchiatti", "in", "charge", "of", "designing", "and", "building", "the", "Palazzo", "Monte", "dei", "Poveri", "Vergognosi", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4, 5], "text": "Congregazione dei Nobili"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [7], "text": "Picchiatti"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "text": "Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Congregazione dei Nobili", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Picchiatti", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Among the buildings of a civil nature can be mentioned the Hacienda Sin Nombre ( With No Name ) , the Hacienda del Burro de Oro ( Golden Donkey ) and the nursing home of San José .", "tokens": ["Among", "the", "buildings", "of", "a", "civil", "nature", "can", "be", "mentioned", "the", "Hacienda", "Sin", "Nombre", "(", "With", "No", "Name", ")", ",", "the", "Hacienda", "del", "Burro", "de", "Oro", "(", "Golden", "Donkey", ")", "and", "the", "nursing", "home", "of", "San", "José", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Hacienda Sin Nombre"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [21, 22, 23, 24, 25], "text": "Hacienda del Burro de Oro"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [27, 28], "text": "Golden Donkey"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [35, 36], "text": "San José"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Hacienda Sin Nombre", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hacienda del Burro de Oro", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Golden Donkey", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "San José", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
