{"text": "Paul International airport .", "tokens": ["Paul", "International", "airport", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "It starred Hicks 's wife , Ellaline Terriss and Edmund Payne .", "tokens": ["It", "starred", "Hicks", "'s", "wife", ",", "Ellaline", "Terriss", "and", "Edmund", "Payne", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [2], "text": "Hicks"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Ellaline Terriss"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Edmund Payne"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Hicks", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Ellaline Terriss", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Edmund Payne", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "`` Time `` magazine said the film was `` a multimillion dollar improvisation that does everything but what the title promises '' and suggested that `` writer George Axelrod ( `` The Seven Year Itch `` ) and director Richard Quine should have taken a hint from Holden [ 's character Richard Benson ] , who writes his movie , takes a long sober look at what he has wrought , and burns it . ''", "tokens": ["``", "Time", "``", "magazine", "said", "the", "film", "was", "``", "a", "multimillion", "dollar", "improvisation", "that", "does", "everything", "but", "what", "the", "title", "promises", "''", "and", "suggested", "that", "``", "writer", "George", "Axelrod", "(", "``", "The", "Seven", "Year", "Itch", "``", ")", "and", "director", "Richard", "Quine", "should", "have", "taken", "a", "hint", "from", "Holden", "[", "'s", "character", "Richard", "Benson", "]", ",", "who", "writes", "his", "movie", ",", "takes", "a", "long", "sober", "look", "at", "what", "he", "has", "wrought", ",", "and", "burns", "it", ".", "''"], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [1], "text": "Time"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [27, 28], "text": "George Axelrod"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [31, 32, 33, 34], "text": "The Seven Year Itch"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [39, 40], "text": "Richard Quine"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [47], "text": "Holden"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [51, 52], "text": "Richard Benson"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Time", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "George Axelrod", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "The Seven Year Itch", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Richard Quine", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Holden", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Richard Benson", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Pakistani scientists and engineers ' working at IAEA became aware of advancing Indian nuclear program towards making the bombs .", "tokens": ["Pakistani", "scientists", "and", "engineers", "'", "working", "at", "IAEA", "became", "aware", "of", "advancing", "Indian", "nuclear", "program", "towards", "making", "the", "bombs", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [7], "text": "IAEA"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "IAEA", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In February 2008 , Church 's Chicken entered the UK market under the `` Texas Chicken `` name , claiming to have signed up 50 former Dixy Chicken franchisees .", "tokens": ["In", "February", "2008", ",", "Church", "'s", "Chicken", "entered", "the", "UK", "market", "under", "the", "``", "Texas", "Chicken", "``", "name", ",", "claiming", "to", "have", "signed", "up", "50", "former", "Dixy", "Chicken", "franchisees", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [4, 5, 6], "text": "Church 's Chicken"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "Texas Chicken"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [26, 27], "text": "Dixy Chicken"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Church 's Chicken", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Texas Chicken", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dixy Chicken", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "This rivalry intensified in 1919 when Arsenal were unexpectedly promoted to the First Division , taking a place that Tottenham believed should be theirs .", "tokens": ["This", "rivalry", "intensified", "in", "1919", "when", "Arsenal", "were", "unexpectedly", "promoted", "to", "the", "First", "Division", ",", "taking", "a", "place", "that", "Tottenham", "believed", "should", "be", "theirs", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [6], "text": "Arsenal"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [12, 13], "text": "First Division"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [19], "text": "Tottenham"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Arsenal", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "First Division", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tottenham", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Seizures often begin as apnea , cyanosis , and hypertonia and last less than 1 minute .", "tokens": ["Seizures", "often", "begin", "as", "apnea", ",", "cyanosis", ",", "and", "hypertonia", "and", "last", "less", "than", "1", "minute", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Only one of four entered Corvettes - GT1 C6R of Luc Alphand Aventures - eventually finished the race , taking second place in class .", "tokens": ["Only", "one", "of", "four", "entered", "Corvettes", "-", "GT1", "C6R", "of", "Luc", "Alphand", "Aventures", "-", "eventually", "finished", "the", "race", ",", "taking", "second", "place", "in", "class", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [5, 6, 7, 8], "text": "Corvettes - GT1 C6R"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [10, 11, 12], "text": "Luc Alphand Aventures"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Corvettes - GT1 C6R", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Luc Alphand Aventures", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He has also written several plays and various articles on the Iranian Constitutional Revolution of 1905-1911 , the French Revolution , and the Russian Revolution .", "tokens": ["He", "has", "also", "written", "several", "plays", "and", "various", "articles", "on", "the", "Iranian", "Constitutional", "Revolution", "of", "1905-1911", ",", "the", "French", "Revolution", ",", "and", "the", "Russian", "Revolution", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Iranian Constitutional Revolution"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "French Revolution"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [23, 24], "text": "Russian Revolution"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Iranian Constitutional Revolution", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "French Revolution", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Russian Revolution", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "After many appeals , the case went to the Supreme Court , which in 1992 ruled in `` Two Pesos , Inc . v . Taco Cabana , Inc . `` in favor of Taco Cabana .", "tokens": ["After", "many", "appeals", ",", "the", "case", "went", "to", "the", "Supreme", "Court", ",", "which", "in", "1992", "ruled", "in", "``", "Two", "Pesos", ",", "Inc", ".", "v", ".", "Taco", "Cabana", ",", "Inc", ".", "``", "in", "favor", "of", "Taco", "Cabana", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Supreme Court"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18, 19, 20, 21, 22], "text": "Two Pesos , Inc ."}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [25, 26, 27, 28, 29], "text": "Taco Cabana , Inc ."}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [34, 35], "text": "Taco Cabana"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Supreme Court", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Two Pesos , Inc .", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Taco Cabana , Inc .", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Taco Cabana", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The army and guards present in the south were also Assyrians .", "tokens": ["The", "army", "and", "guards", "present", "in", "the", "south", "were", "also", "Assyrians", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Imelda de ' Lambertazzi is a `` melodramma tragico '' or tragic opera in two acts by Gaetano Donizett i from a libretto by Andrea Leone Tottola , based on the tragedy `` Imelda '' by Gabriele Sperduti .", "tokens": ["Imelda", "de", "'", "Lambertazzi", "is", "a", "``", "melodramma", "tragico", "''", "or", "tragic", "opera", "in", "two", "acts", "by", "Gaetano", "Donizett", "i", "from", "a", "libretto", "by", "Andrea", "Leone", "Tottola", ",", "based", "on", "the", "tragedy", "``", "Imelda", "''", "by", "Gabriele", "Sperduti", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [0, 1, 2, 3], "text": "Imelda de ' Lambertazzi"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Gaetano Donizett"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [24, 25, 26], "text": "Andrea Leone Tottola"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [33, 34, 35, 36, 37], "text": "Imelda '' by Gabriele Sperduti"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Imelda de ' Lambertazzi", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Gaetano Donizett", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Andrea Leone Tottola", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Imelda '' by Gabriele Sperduti", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Amphiphysin is a brain-enriched protein with an N-terminal lipid interaction , dimerisation and membrane bending BAR domain , a middle clathrin and adaptor binding domain and a C-terminal SH3 domain .", "tokens": ["Amphiphysin", "is", "a", "brain-enriched", "protein", "with", "an", "N-terminal", "lipid", "interaction", ",", "dimerisation", "and", "membrane", "bending", "BAR", "domain", ",", "a", "middle", "clathrin", "and", "adaptor", "binding", "domain", "and", "a", "C-terminal", "SH3", "domain", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [0], "text": "Amphiphysin"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "N-terminal lipid"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [15], "text": "BAR"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [27, 28, 29], "text": "C-terminal SH3 domain"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Amphiphysin", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "N-terminal lipid", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "BAR", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "C-terminal SH3 domain", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Decorations and awards can be conferred on Croatian or foreign nationals , legal entities as well as units of the Armed Forces of the Republic of Croatia and the Ministry of the Interior .", "tokens": ["Decorations", "and", "awards", "can", "be", "conferred", "on", "Croatian", "or", "foreign", "nationals", ",", "legal", "entities", "as", "well", "as", "units", "of", "the", "Armed", "Forces", "of", "the", "Republic", "of", "Croatia", "and", "the", "Ministry", "of", "the", "Interior", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [7], "text": "Croatian"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [23, 24, 25, 26], "text": "the Republic of Croatia"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Croatian", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "the Republic of Croatia", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The pandemic affected the Mediterranean Basin most severely and most frequently , but also infected the Near East and Northern Europe .", "tokens": ["The", "pandemic", "affected", "the", "Mediterranean", "Basin", "most", "severely", "and", "most", "frequently", ",", "but", "also", "infected", "the", "Near", "East", "and", "Northern", "Europe", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "Mediterranean Basin"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "Near East"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "Northern Europe"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Mediterranean Basin", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Near East", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Northern Europe", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The rivalry began to heat up in the early 2000s .", "tokens": ["The", "rivalry", "began", "to", "heat", "up", "in", "the", "early", "2000s", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "In 1783 Campbell married Olympia Elizabeth ( died 1794 ) , eldest daughter of William Morshead of Cartuther , Cornwall .", "tokens": ["In", "1783", "Campbell", "married", "Olympia", "Elizabeth", "(", "died", "1794", ")", ",", "eldest", "daughter", "of", "William", "Morshead", "of", "Cartuther", ",", "Cornwall", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [2], "text": "Campbell"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "Olympia Elizabeth"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "William Morshead"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "Cartuther"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19], "text": "Cornwall"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Campbell", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Olympia Elizabeth", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "William Morshead", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Cartuther", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Cornwall", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "From her locations Mrs. Strong created papers for the Duke of Windsor and Wallis , The Duchess of Windsor , Barbara Hutton , the Rockefeller , Astor , Vanderbilt , and DuPont families , as well as Bette Davis , Diana Vreeland , Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy , Barbara Paley , and other icons of style .", "tokens": ["From", "her", "locations", "Mrs.", "Strong", "created", "papers", "for", "the", "Duke", "of", "Windsor", "and", "Wallis", ",", "The", "Duchess", "of", "Windsor", ",", "Barbara", "Hutton", ",", "the", "Rockefeller", ",", "Astor", ",", "Vanderbilt", ",", "and", "DuPont", "families", ",", "as", "well", "as", "Bette", "Davis", ",", "Diana", "Vreeland", ",", "Jacqueline", "Bouvier", "Kennedy", ",", "Barbara", "Paley", ",", "and", "other", "icons", "of", "style", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Mrs. Strong"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11], "text": "Windsor"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [13], "text": "Wallis"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [18], "text": "Windsor"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [20, 21], "text": "Barbara Hutton"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [24], "text": "Rockefeller"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [26], "text": "Astor"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [28], "text": "Vanderbilt"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [31], "text": "DuPont"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [37, 38], "text": "Bette Davis"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [40, 41], "text": "Diana Vreeland"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [43, 44, 45], "text": "Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [47, 48], "text": "Barbara Paley"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Mrs. Strong", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Windsor", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Wallis", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Windsor", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Barbara Hutton", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Rockefeller", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Astor", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Vanderbilt", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "DuPont", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bette Davis", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Diana Vreeland", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Jacqueline Bouvier Kennedy", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Barbara Paley", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "As a result of outdoing the competition , Binion received death threats , although eventually casinos raised their limits to keep up with him .", "tokens": ["As", "a", "result", "of", "outdoing", "the", "competition", ",", "Binion", "received", "death", "threats", ",", "although", "eventually", "casinos", "raised", "their", "limits", "to", "keep", "up", "with", "him", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [8], "text": "Binion"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Binion", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Its title is also seen as The Gale Storm Show : Oh , Susanna .", "tokens": ["Its", "title", "is", "also", "seen", "as", "The", "Gale", "Storm", "Show", ":", "Oh", ",", "Susanna", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13], "text": "The Gale Storm Show : Oh , Susanna"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "The Gale Storm Show : Oh , Susanna", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Known locally as `` Fairbottom Bobs `` it is now preserved at the Henry Ford Museum in Dearborn , Michigan .", "tokens": ["Known", "locally", "as", "``", "Fairbottom", "Bobs", "``", "it", "is", "now", "preserved", "at", "the", "Henry", "Ford", "Museum", "in", "Dearborn", ",", "Michigan", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "Fairbottom Bobs"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [13, 14, 15], "text": "Henry Ford Museum"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "Dearborn"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19], "text": "Michigan"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Fairbottom Bobs", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Henry Ford Museum", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dearborn", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Michigan", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Sheremetyevo International Airport has four operating passenger terminals and one special terminal reserved for the use of private and business aviation .", "tokens": ["Sheremetyevo", "International", "Airport", "has", "four", "operating", "passenger", "terminals", "and", "one", "special", "terminal", "reserved", "for", "the", "use", "of", "private", "and", "business", "aviation", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "Sheremetyevo International Airport"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sheremetyevo International Airport", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Using `` bite-and-hold '' tactics , with objectives limited to what could be held against German counter-attacks , the British devastated the German defence , which prompted a crisis among the German commanders and caused a severe loss of morale in the 4th Army .", "tokens": ["Using", "``", "bite-and-hold", "''", "tactics", ",", "with", "objectives", "limited", "to", "what", "could", "be", "held", "against", "German", "counter-attacks", ",", "the", "British", "devastated", "the", "German", "defence", ",", "which", "prompted", "a", "crisis", "among", "the", "German", "commanders", "and", "caused", "a", "severe", "loss", "of", "morale", "in", "the", "4th", "Army", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "German"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19], "text": "British"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "German"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [31], "text": "German"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [42, 43], "text": "4th Army"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "German", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "British", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "German", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "German", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "4th Army", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "During medical school , Reitman often worked as the house doctor at sporting events at the Boston Garden .", "tokens": ["During", "medical", "school", ",", "Reitman", "often", "worked", "as", "the", "house", "doctor", "at", "sporting", "events", "at", "the", "Boston", "Garden", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4], "text": "Reitman"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "Boston Garden"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Reitman", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Boston Garden", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Normally , when the new window appears , it displays the same buffer as the previous one .", "tokens": ["Normally", ",", "when", "the", "new", "window", "appears", ",", "it", "displays", "the", "same", "buffer", "as", "the", "previous", "one", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Formerly known as the Communiplex , it is home to the WHL 's Prince Albert Raiders and the Prince Albert Mintos .", "tokens": ["Formerly", "known", "as", "the", "Communiplex", ",", "it", "is", "home", "to", "the", "WHL", "'s", "Prince", "Albert", "Raiders", "and", "the", "Prince", "Albert", "Mintos", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [4], "text": "Communiplex"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [11], "text": "WHL"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "Albert Raiders"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "Albert Mintos"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Communiplex", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "WHL", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Albert Raiders", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Albert Mintos", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The chapel of Stalmine was first mentioned about 1200 and a cemetery was consecrated in 1230 .", "tokens": ["The", "chapel", "of", "Stalmine", "was", "first", "mentioned", "about", "1200", "and", "a", "cemetery", "was", "consecrated", "in", "1230", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3], "text": "Stalmine"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Stalmine", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The score to `` Spring Breakdown '' was composed by Deborah Lurie who recorded her score with the Hollywood Studio Symphony conducted by Blake Neely and recorded by Greg Dennen at the Eastwood Scoring Stage at Warner Brothers .", "tokens": ["The", "score", "to", "``", "Spring", "Breakdown", "''", "was", "composed", "by", "Deborah", "Lurie", "who", "recorded", "her", "score", "with", "the", "Hollywood", "Studio", "Symphony", "conducted", "by", "Blake", "Neely", "and", "recorded", "by", "Greg", "Dennen", "at", "the", "Eastwood", "Scoring", "Stage", "at", "Warner", "Brothers", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Deborah Lurie"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [18, 19, 20], "text": "Hollywood Studio Symphony"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [23, 24], "text": "Blake Neely"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [28, 29], "text": "Greg Dennen"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [32, 33, 34], "text": "Eastwood Scoring Stage"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [36, 37], "text": "Warner Brothers"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization", "event", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Deborah Lurie", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hollywood Studio Symphony", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Blake Neely", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Greg Dennen", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Eastwood Scoring Stage", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Warner Brothers", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Dozens of brands appeared on drugstore shelves , in numerous formulations .", "tokens": ["Dozens", "of", "brands", "appeared", "on", "drugstore", "shelves", ",", "in", "numerous", "formulations", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The Swedish national men 's ice hockey team , affectionately known as `` Tre Kronor `` ( English : Three Crowns ; the national symbol of Sweden ) , is regarded as one of the best in the world .", "tokens": ["The", "Swedish", "national", "men", "'s", "ice", "hockey", "team", ",", "affectionately", "known", "as", "``", "Tre", "Kronor", "``", "(", "English", ":", "Three", "Crowns", ";", "the", "national", "symbol", "of", "Sweden", ")", ",", "is", "regarded", "as", "one", "of", "the", "best", "in", "the", "world", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7], "text": "Swedish national men 's ice hockey team"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "Tre Kronor"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [17], "text": "English"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "Three Crowns"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [26], "text": "Sweden"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other", "organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Swedish national men 's ice hockey team", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tre Kronor", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "English", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Three Crowns", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Sweden", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Significant technical and materials problems were encountered with FBRs , and geological exploration showed that scarcity of uranium was not going to be a concern for some time .", "tokens": ["Significant", "technical", "and", "materials", "problems", "were", "encountered", "with", "FBRs", ",", "and", "geological", "exploration", "showed", "that", "scarcity", "of", "uranium", "was", "not", "going", "to", "be", "a", "concern", "for", "some", "time", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [17], "text": "uranium"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "uranium", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 1992 , another film adaptation of the novel was made , `` L'Atlantide `` , directed by Bob Swaim and starring Tchéky Karyo , Jean Rochefort , Anna Galiena , and the famous Spanish actor , Fernando Rey .", "tokens": ["In", "1992", ",", "another", "film", "adaptation", "of", "the", "novel", "was", "made", ",", "``", "L'Atlantide", "``", ",", "directed", "by", "Bob", "Swaim", "and", "starring", "Tchéky", "Karyo", ",", "Jean", "Rochefort", ",", "Anna", "Galiena", ",", "and", "the", "famous", "Spanish", "actor", ",", "Fernando", "Rey", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [13], "text": "L'Atlantide"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "Bob Swaim"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Tchéky Karyo"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [25, 26], "text": "Jean Rochefort"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [28, 29], "text": "Anna Galiena"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [34], "text": "Spanish"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [37, 38], "text": "Fernando Rey"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "L'Atlantide", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bob Swaim", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tchéky Karyo", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Jean Rochefort", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Anna Galiena", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Spanish", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Fernando Rey", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Audi in fourth and Jaguar in fifth were separated by one point .", "tokens": ["Audi", "in", "fourth", "and", "Jaguar", "in", "fifth", "were", "separated", "by", "one", "point", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [0], "text": "Audi"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [4], "text": "Jaguar"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Audi", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Jaguar", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Chiltern Air Support 's Luton helicopter ( EC135T2 CPDS ) moved from London Luton Airport to RAF Henlow , near Hitchin and Shillington .", "tokens": ["Chiltern", "Air", "Support", "'s", "Luton", "helicopter", "(", "EC135T2", "CPDS", ")", "moved", "from", "London", "Luton", "Airport", "to", "RAF", "Henlow", ",", "near", "Hitchin", "and", "Shillington", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "Chiltern Air Support"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [4], "text": "Luton"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "EC135T2 CPDS"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "London"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "Luton Airport"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "RAF Henlow"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [20], "text": "Hitchin"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "Shillington"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Chiltern Air Support", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Luton", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "EC135T2 CPDS", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Luton Airport", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "RAF Henlow", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hitchin", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Shillington", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "This song was recorded in Puerto Rico at the Alpha Recording Studios .", "tokens": ["This", "song", "was", "recorded", "in", "Puerto", "Rico", "at", "the", "Alpha", "Recording", "Studios", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [5, 6], "text": "Puerto Rico"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [9, 10, 11], "text": "Alpha Recording Studios"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Puerto Rico", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Alpha Recording Studios", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "For freighter destinations see Air China Cargo .", "tokens": ["For", "freighter", "destinations", "see", "Air", "China", "Cargo", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Planned to connect Downtown Newark and Elizabeth via Newark Liberty International Airport , NJT is no longer pursuing the Newark-Elizabeth Rail Link .", "tokens": ["Planned", "to", "connect", "Downtown", "Newark", "and", "Elizabeth", "via", "Newark", "Liberty", "International", "Airport", ",", "NJT", "is", "no", "longer", "pursuing", "the", "Newark-Elizabeth", "Rail", "Link", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [4], "text": "Newark"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [6], "text": "Elizabeth"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [8, 9, 10, 11], "text": "Newark Liberty International Airport"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [13], "text": "NJT"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19, 20, 21], "text": "Newark-Elizabeth Rail Link"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Newark", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Elizabeth", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Newark Liberty International Airport", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NJT", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Newark-Elizabeth Rail Link", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "On 25 April , Krukenberg was appointed by General Helmuth Weidling as the commander of ( Berlin ) Defence Sector C , which included the SS Division Nordland , whose previous commander Joachim Ziegler was relieved of his command the same day .", "tokens": ["On", "25", "April", ",", "Krukenberg", "was", "appointed", "by", "General", "Helmuth", "Weidling", "as", "the", "commander", "of", "(", "Berlin", ")", "Defence", "Sector", "C", ",", "which", "included", "the", "SS", "Division", "Nordland", ",", "whose", "previous", "commander", "Joachim", "Ziegler", "was", "relieved", "of", "his", "command", "the", "same", "day", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4], "text": "Krukenberg"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Helmuth Weidling"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16], "text": "Berlin"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18, 19, 20], "text": "Defence Sector C"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [25, 26, 27], "text": "SS Division Nordland"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [32, 33], "text": "Joachim Ziegler"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Krukenberg", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Helmuth Weidling", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Berlin", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Defence Sector C", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "SS Division Nordland", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Joachim Ziegler", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "To enforce the injunction , Quixtar filed an action against 30 anonymous bloggers .", "tokens": ["To", "enforce", "the", "injunction", ",", "Quixtar", "filed", "an", "action", "against", "30", "anonymous", "bloggers", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [5], "text": "Quixtar"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Quixtar", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Eighth Army began to attack Italian units , located using information from Ultra , at Ruweisat Ridge and from again at Tel El Eisa on 22 July and Miteirya Ridge after which another lull fell .", "tokens": ["The", "Eighth", "Army", "began", "to", "attack", "Italian", "units", ",", "located", "using", "information", "from", "Ultra", ",", "at", "Ruweisat", "Ridge", "and", "from", "again", "at", "Tel", "El", "Eisa", "on", "22", "July", "and", "Miteirya", "Ridge", "after", "which", "another", "lull", "fell", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "Eighth Army"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [6], "text": "Italian"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "Ruweisat Ridge"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22, 23, 24], "text": "Tel El Eisa"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [29, 30], "text": "Miteirya Ridge"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Eighth Army", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Italian", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Ruweisat Ridge", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tel El Eisa", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Miteirya Ridge", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Hoey was born in Mallusk , County Antrim , and studied at Belfast Royal Academy and the Ulster College of Physical Education .", "tokens": ["Hoey", "was", "born", "in", "Mallusk", ",", "County", "Antrim", ",", "and", "studied", "at", "Belfast", "Royal", "Academy", "and", "the", "Ulster", "College", "of", "Physical", "Education", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Hoey"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [4], "text": "Mallusk"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "County Antrim"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21], "text": "Belfast Royal Academy and the Ulster College of Physical Education"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Hoey", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mallusk", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "County Antrim", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Belfast Royal Academy and the Ulster College of Physical Education", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 1963 Leicester City Council ( LCC ) , identifying a gap in cultural provision for live performances , built a 262-seat theatre in Leicester .", "tokens": ["In", "1963", "Leicester", "City", "Council", "(", "LCC", ")", ",", "identifying", "a", "gap", "in", "cultural", "provision", "for", "live", "performances", ",", "built", "a", "262-seat", "theatre", "in", "Leicester", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [2, 3, 4], "text": "Leicester City Council"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24], "text": "Leicester"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Leicester City Council", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Leicester", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He plays Chief Irvin Irving on Amazon Prime 's `` Bosch `` .", "tokens": ["He", "plays", "Chief", "Irvin", "Irving", "on", "Amazon", "Prime", "'s", "``", "Bosch", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Irvin Irving"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Amazon Prime"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [10], "text": "Bosch"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Irvin Irving", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Amazon Prime", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bosch", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "10th century ) was a Chinese landscape painter of the late Five Dynasties and Ten Kingdoms and early Northern Song periods .", "tokens": ["10th", "century", ")", "was", "a", "Chinese", "landscape", "painter", "of", "the", "late", "Five", "Dynasties", "and", "Ten", "Kingdoms", "and", "early", "Northern", "Song", "periods", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [5], "text": "Chinese"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Chinese", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 2010 , Al Jazeera 's Teymoor Nabili suggested that the article `` Cyrus Cylinder '' had been edited for political purposes by `` an apparent tussle of opinions in the shadowy world of hard drives and 'independent ' editors that comprise the Wikipedia industry . ''", "tokens": ["In", "2010", ",", "Al", "Jazeera", "'s", "Teymoor", "Nabili", "suggested", "that", "the", "article", "``", "Cyrus", "Cylinder", "''", "had", "been", "edited", "for", "political", "purposes", "by", "``", "an", "apparent", "tussle", "of", "opinions", "in", "the", "shadowy", "world", "of", "hard", "drives", "and", "'independent", "'", "editors", "that", "comprise", "the", "Wikipedia", "industry", ".", "''"], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Al Jazeera"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Teymoor Nabili"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [43], "text": "Wikipedia"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Al Jazeera", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Teymoor Nabili", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Wikipedia", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Church of England parish church of St John The Evangelist in Friern Barnet Road is Grade II * listed .", "tokens": ["The", "Church", "of", "England", "parish", "church", "of", "St", "John", "The", "Evangelist", "in", "Friern", "Barnet", "Road", "is", "Grade", "II", "*", "listed", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10], "text": "Church of England parish church of St John The Evangelist"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12, 13, 14], "text": "Friern Barnet Road"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Church of England parish church of St John The Evangelist", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Friern Barnet Road", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The new Samsat district is a peninsula surrounded on the three sides by the Atatürk Dam Lake .", "tokens": ["The", "new", "Samsat", "district", "is", "a", "peninsula", "surrounded", "on", "the", "three", "sides", "by", "the", "Atatürk", "Dam", "Lake", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [1, 2, 3], "text": "new Samsat district"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14, 15, 16], "text": "Atatürk Dam Lake"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "new Samsat district", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Atatürk Dam Lake", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The drill hall is long and has two tall mansard towers .", "tokens": ["The", "drill", "hall", "is", "long", "and", "has", "two", "tall", "mansard", "towers", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "The drill hall"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "The drill hall", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "As a protest , the incumbent Helikopter Service applied for the airline routes that Braathens SAFE operated from Stavanger , but this application was rejected .", "tokens": ["As", "a", "protest", ",", "the", "incumbent", "Helikopter", "Service", "applied", "for", "the", "airline", "routes", "that", "Braathens", "SAFE", "operated", "from", "Stavanger", ",", "but", "this", "application", "was", "rejected", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "Braathens SAFE"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [18], "text": "Stavanger"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Braathens SAFE", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stavanger", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He was a European professional basketball player in Germany from 1998-1999 .", "tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "European", "professional", "basketball", "player", "in", "Germany", "from", "1998-1999", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [3], "text": "European"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Germany"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "European", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Germany", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The bascule bridge carries NJ Transit Rail Operations North Jersey Coast Line between the Bradley Beach and Belmar stations .", "tokens": ["The", "bascule", "bridge", "carries", "NJ", "Transit", "Rail", "Operations", "North", "Jersey", "Coast", "Line", "between", "the", "Bradley", "Beach", "and", "Belmar", "stations", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [4, 5, 6, 7], "text": "NJ Transit Rail Operations"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8, 9, 10, 11], "text": "North Jersey Coast Line"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "Bradley Beach"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Belmar stations"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "NJ Transit Rail Operations", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "North Jersey Coast Line", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bradley Beach", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Belmar stations", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Bayerische Staatsbibliothek furthermore is Europe 's second-largest journals library ( after the British Library ) .", "tokens": ["The", "Bayerische", "Staatsbibliothek", "furthermore", "is", "Europe", "'s", "second-largest", "journals", "library", "(", "after", "the", "British", "Library", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "Bayerische Staatsbibliothek"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [5], "text": "Europe"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "British Library"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bayerische Staatsbibliothek", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Europe", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "British Library", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Outerbridge Crossing , which opened to traffic on June 29 , 1928 , is a cantilever bridge over the Arthur Kill that connects Perth Amboy with Staten Island .", "tokens": ["The", "Outerbridge", "Crossing", ",", "which", "opened", "to", "traffic", "on", "June", "29", ",", "1928", ",", "is", "a", "cantilever", "bridge", "over", "the", "Arthur", "Kill", "that", "connects", "Perth", "Amboy", "with", "Staten", "Island", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "The Outerbridge Crossing"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [20, 21], "text": "Arthur Kill"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24, 25], "text": "Perth Amboy"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [27, 28], "text": "Staten Island"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "The Outerbridge Crossing", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Arthur Kill", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Perth Amboy", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Staten Island", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Raisna Chauhan is a village in the Meerut district of Uttar Pradesh state , India , and forms a part of the National Capital Region ( NCR ) .", "tokens": ["Raisna", "Chauhan", "is", "a", "village", "in", "the", "Meerut", "district", "of", "Uttar", "Pradesh", "state", ",", "India", ",", "and", "forms", "a", "part", "of", "the", "National", "Capital", "Region", "(", "NCR", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Raisna Chauhan"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "Meerut district"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Uttar Pradesh"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14], "text": "India"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27], "text": "National Capital Region ( NCR )"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Raisna Chauhan", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Meerut district", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Uttar Pradesh", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "India", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "National Capital Region ( NCR )", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The law proposed to establish a corporativist state .", "tokens": ["The", "law", "proposed", "to", "establish", "a", "corporativist", "state", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "In 1654 the Congregazione dei Nobili put Picchiatti in charge of designing and building the Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi .", "tokens": ["In", "1654", "the", "Congregazione", "dei", "Nobili", "put", "Picchiatti", "in", "charge", "of", "designing", "and", "building", "the", "Palazzo", "Monte", "dei", "Poveri", "Vergognosi", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4, 5], "text": "Congregazione dei Nobili"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [7], "text": "Picchiatti"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "text": "Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Congregazione dei Nobili", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Picchiatti", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Palazzo Monte dei Poveri Vergognosi", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "While considerably reduced , the Papal States nevertheless still covered the Latium and large areas northwest of Rome .", "tokens": ["While", "considerably", "reduced", ",", "the", "Papal", "States", "nevertheless", "still", "covered", "the", "Latium", "and", "large", "areas", "northwest", "of", "Rome", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [5, 6], "text": "Papal States"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [11], "text": "Latium"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "Rome"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Papal States", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Latium", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Rome", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "All seven packages were won by the incumbent operator Widerøe .", "tokens": ["All", "seven", "packages", "were", "won", "by", "the", "incumbent", "operator", "Widerøe", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "This was part of a wider Bicentennial Boycott movement which started in the leadup to the Bicentennial .", "tokens": ["This", "was", "part", "of", "a", "wider", "Bicentennial", "Boycott", "movement", "which", "started", "in", "the", "leadup", "to", "the", "Bicentennial", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [6, 7, 8], "text": "Bicentennial Boycott movement"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16], "text": "Bicentennial"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bicentennial Boycott movement", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bicentennial", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Laccadives are different in structure from the Maldives .", "tokens": ["The", "Laccadives", "are", "different", "in", "structure", "from", "the", "Maldives", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [1], "text": "Laccadives"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Maldives"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Laccadives", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Maldives", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Broch of West Burrafirth is an Iron Age broch located on the west side of Mainland , Shetland ( ) .", "tokens": ["The", "Broch", "of", "West", "Burrafirth", "is", "an", "Iron", "Age", "broch", "located", "on", "the", "west", "side", "of", "Mainland", ",", "Shetland", "(", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "West Burrafirth"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16], "text": "Mainland"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [18], "text": "Shetland"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "West Burrafirth", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mainland", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Shetland", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "As a senior , he hit .277 , tied for the team lead with six home runs .", "tokens": ["As", "a", "senior", ",", "he", "hit", ".277", ",", "tied", "for", "the", "team", "lead", "with", "six", "home", "runs", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Prior to issuing AR-15 's , The Patrol began participating in a program with the US Government and purchased surplus M-14 rifles .", "tokens": ["Prior", "to", "issuing", "AR-15", "'s", ",", "The", "Patrol", "began", "participating", "in", "a", "program", "with", "the", "US", "Government", "and", "purchased", "surplus", "M-14", "rifles", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "AR-15 's"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "US"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [20], "text": "M-14"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "AR-15 's", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "US", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "M-14", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The game 's source code was shared with other institutions with a PDP-1 across the country as the MIT students themselves moved about , allowing the game to gain popularity .", "tokens": ["The", "game", "'s", "source", "code", "was", "shared", "with", "other", "institutions", "with", "a", "PDP-1", "across", "the", "country", "as", "the", "MIT", "students", "themselves", "moved", "about", ",", "allowing", "the", "game", "to", "gain", "popularity", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [12], "text": "PDP-1"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18], "text": "MIT"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "PDP-1", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "MIT", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "12 Corazones ( , `` 12 Hearts '' ) is a Spanish -language dating game show produced in the United States for the television network Telemundo since January 2005 , based on its namesake Argentine TV show format The show is filmed in Los Angeles and revolves around the twelve Zodiac signs that identify each contestant .", "tokens": ["12", "Corazones", "(", ",", "``", "12", "Hearts", "''", ")", "is", "a", "Spanish", "-language", "dating", "game", "show", "produced", "in", "the", "United", "States", "for", "the", "television", "network", "Telemundo", "since", "January", "2005", ",", "based", "on", "its", "namesake", "Argentine", "TV", "show", "format", "The", "show", "is", "filmed", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "and", "revolves", "around", "the", "twelve", "Zodiac", "signs", "that", "identify", "each", "contestant", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [1], "text": "Corazones"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11], "text": "Spanish"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "United States"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [34, 35], "text": "Argentine TV"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [43, 44], "text": "Los Angeles"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [50], "text": "Zodiac"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "other", "organization", "person", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Corazones", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Spanish", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "United States", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Argentine TV", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Los Angeles", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Zodiac", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The coachbuilder and seller was Hooper & amp ; Co . in London .", "tokens": ["The", "coachbuilder", "and", "seller", "was", "Hooper", "&", "amp", ";", "Co", ".", "in", "London", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10], "text": "Hooper & amp ; Co ."}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "London"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Hooper & amp ; Co .", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "She was a younger sister of Emeric , King of Hungary .", "tokens": ["She", "was", "a", "younger", "sister", "of", "Emeric", ",", "King", "of", "Hungary", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6], "text": "Emeric"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [10], "text": "Hungary"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Emeric", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hungary", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Though only in length , The Salamander Glacier is about wide .", "tokens": ["Though", "only", "in", "length", ",", "The", "Salamander", "Glacier", "is", "about", "wide", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Salamander Glacier"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Salamander Glacier", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The video , shot in Los Angeles on location at The Echo , The Standard Hotel and the streets of Downtown LA , was premiered by UK music tastemaker Clash ( magazine ) .", "tokens": ["The", "video", ",", "shot", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "on", "location", "at", "The", "Echo", ",", "The", "Standard", "Hotel", "and", "the", "streets", "of", "Downtown", "LA", ",", "was", "premiered", "by", "UK", "music", "tastemaker", "Clash", "(", "magazine", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [5, 6], "text": "Los Angeles"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "The Echo"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [13, 14, 15], "text": "The Standard Hotel"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [21], "text": "LA"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [26], "text": "UK"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [29], "text": "Clash"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Los Angeles", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "The Echo", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "The Standard Hotel", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "LA", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "UK", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Clash", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "State Route 151 ( SR 151 ) is a state highway in the U.S . state of California .", "tokens": ["State", "Route", "151", "(", "SR", "151", ")", "is", "a", "state", "highway", "in", "the", "U.S", ".", "state", "of", "California", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "State Route 151"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "U.S ."}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "California"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "State Route 151", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "U.S .", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "California", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Based initially at Cley next the Sea , it moved to Sheringham in mid-1918 and remained on the Norfolk coast until disbandment on 24 March 1919 .", "tokens": ["Based", "initially", "at", "Cley", "next", "the", "Sea", ",", "it", "moved", "to", "Sheringham", "in", "mid-1918", "and", "remained", "on", "the", "Norfolk", "coast", "until", "disbandment", "on", "24", "March", "1919", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [3], "text": "Cley"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [11], "text": "Sheringham"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "Norfolk coast"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Cley", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Sheringham", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Norfolk coast", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "On May 4 , 2013 , the light was reactivated and has been operated seasonally ever since .", "tokens": ["On", "May", "4", ",", "2013", ",", "the", "light", "was", "reactivated", "and", "has", "been", "operated", "seasonally", "ever", "since", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "`` It gives a good impression in terms of technology , solidarity and efficiency . ''", "tokens": ["``", "It", "gives", "a", "good", "impression", "in", "terms", "of", "technology", ",", "solidarity", "and", "efficiency", ".", "''"], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The King-Emperor , George V , released him in 1920 as the result of a general amnesty order .", "tokens": ["The", "King-Emperor", ",", "George", "V", ",", "released", "him", "in", "1920", "as", "the", "result", "of", "a", "general", "amnesty", "order", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "George V"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "George V", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "It is now home to the Fort George Island Visitor Center .", "tokens": ["It", "is", "now", "home", "to", "the", "Fort", "George", "Island", "Visitor", "Center", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10], "text": "Fort George Island Visitor Center"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Fort George Island Visitor Center", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Despite the title `` hammerless '' , the Model 1903 does have a hammer .", "tokens": ["Despite", "the", "title", "``", "hammerless", "''", ",", "the", "Model", "1903", "does", "have", "a", "hammer", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Since 1989 until his death , he was a member of the Masaryk Democratic Movement .", "tokens": ["Since", "1989", "until", "his", "death", ",", "he", "was", "a", "member", "of", "the", "Masaryk", "Democratic", "Movement", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [12, 13, 14], "text": "Masaryk Democratic Movement"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Masaryk Democratic Movement", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "This building , also restored by John McAslan + Partners , houses a restaurant , art galleries , meeting rooms , shop , visitor reception and administration offices .", "tokens": ["This", "building", ",", "also", "restored", "by", "John", "McAslan", "+", "Partners", ",", "houses", "a", "restaurant", ",", "art", "galleries", ",", "meeting", "rooms", ",", "shop", ",", "visitor", "reception", "and", "administration", "offices", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9], "text": "John McAslan + Partners"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "John McAslan + Partners", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "L.C .", "tokens": ["L.C", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Although the field was designed originally to serve only municipal civil airport needs , it had an Air Force connection almost from the beginning .", "tokens": ["Although", "the", "field", "was", "designed", "originally", "to", "serve", "only", "municipal", "civil", "airport", "needs", ",", "it", "had", "an", "Air", "Force", "connection", "almost", "from", "the", "beginning", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Bruno Zanoni ( born 29 July 1952 ) is an Italian racing cyclist .", "tokens": ["Bruno", "Zanoni", "(", "born", "29", "July", "1952", ")", "is", "an", "Italian", "racing", "cyclist", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Bruno Zanoni"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [10], "text": "Italian"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bruno Zanoni", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Italian", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Griffis defeated Ernie Johnson to challenge Mallen .", "tokens": ["Griffis", "defeated", "Ernie", "Johnson", "to", "challenge", "Mallen", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Griffis"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [2, 3], "text": "Ernie Johnson"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [6], "text": "Mallen"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Griffis", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Ernie Johnson", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mallen", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Men in Her Diary is a 1945 American comedy film .", "tokens": ["Men", "in", "Her", "Diary", "is", "a", "1945", "American", "comedy", "film", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [0, 1, 2, 3], "text": "Men in Her Diary"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [7], "text": "American"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Men in Her Diary", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "American", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "`` Fliegerkorps '' under Generaloberst Bruno Loerzer at Frankfurt , and V. `` Fliegerkorps '' under command of General Robert Ritter von Greim at Gersthofen .", "tokens": ["``", "Fliegerkorps", "''", "under", "Generaloberst", "Bruno", "Loerzer", "at", "Frankfurt", ",", "and", "V.", "``", "Fliegerkorps", "''", "under", "command", "of", "General", "Robert", "Ritter", "von", "Greim", "at", "Gersthofen", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [5, 6], "text": "Bruno Loerzer"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Frankfurt"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [11, 12, 13, 14], "text": "V. `` Fliegerkorps ''"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [19, 20, 21, 22], "text": "Robert Ritter von Greim"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24], "text": "Gersthofen"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bruno Loerzer", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Frankfurt", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "V. `` Fliegerkorps ''", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Robert Ritter von Greim", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Gersthofen", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He left for Italy in April 1857 and also visited Greece before returning to France in 1861 .", "tokens": ["He", "left", "for", "Italy", "in", "April", "1857", "and", "also", "visited", "Greece", "before", "returning", "to", "France", "in", "1861", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [10], "text": "Greece"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14], "text": "France"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Greece", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "France", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The non-stop service is offered between Zhuhai and Guangzhou South only , and travel between Zhuhai ( Gongbei ) and Zhuhai Airport will be cut down to 25 minutes .", "tokens": ["The", "non-stop", "service", "is", "offered", "between", "Zhuhai", "and", "Guangzhou", "South", "only", ",", "and", "travel", "between", "Zhuhai", "(", "Gongbei", ")", "and", "Zhuhai", "Airport", "will", "be", "cut", "down", "to", "25", "minutes", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [6], "text": "Zhuhai"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8, 9], "text": "Guangzhou South"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "Zhuhai"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "Gongbei"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [20, 21], "text": "Zhuhai Airport"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Zhuhai", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Guangzhou South", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Zhuhai", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Gongbei", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Zhuhai Airport", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Although the game features his name , Tom Clancy had little to no involvement in the development of any of the Splinter Cell games .", "tokens": ["Although", "the", "game", "features", "his", "name", ",", "Tom", "Clancy", "had", "little", "to", "no", "involvement", "in", "the", "development", "of", "any", "of", "the", "Splinter", "Cell", "games", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "Tom Clancy"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [21, 22], "text": "Splinter Cell"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Tom Clancy", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Splinter Cell", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The C. E. Toberman Estate , also known as Villa Las Colinas , is a gated Mission Revival mansion and estate on Camino Palmero in Hollywood , Los Angeles , California .", "tokens": ["The", "C.", "E.", "Toberman", "Estate", ",", "also", "known", "as", "Villa", "Las", "Colinas", ",", "is", "a", "gated", "Mission", "Revival", "mansion", "and", "estate", "on", "Camino", "Palmero", "in", "Hollywood", ",", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "California", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [1, 2, 3, 4], "text": "C. E. Toberman Estate"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [9, 10, 11], "text": "Villa Las Colinas"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [16, 17, 18], "text": "Mission Revival mansion"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Camino Palmero"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [25], "text": "Hollywood"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [27, 28], "text": "Los Angeles"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [30], "text": "California"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "C. E. Toberman Estate", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Villa Las Colinas", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mission Revival mansion", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Camino Palmero", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hollywood", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Los Angeles", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "California", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Mount Diablo has inspired many artists and writers .", "tokens": ["Mount", "Diablo", "has", "inspired", "many", "artists", "and", "writers", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Mount Diablo"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Mount Diablo", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Nevertheless , an extensive `` guardianship '' was given to clerics .", "tokens": ["Nevertheless", ",", "an", "extensive", "``", "guardianship", "''", "was", "given", "to", "clerics", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The Thirty Years ' Peace was a treaty signed between the ancient Greek city-states of Athens and Sparta in 446/445 BCE .", "tokens": ["The", "Thirty", "Years", "'", "Peace", "was", "a", "treaty", "signed", "between", "the", "ancient", "Greek", "city-states", "of", "Athens", "and", "Sparta", "in", "446/445", "BCE", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [1, 2, 3, 4], "text": "Thirty Years ' Peace"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "Greek"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "Athens"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [17], "text": "Sparta"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Thirty Years ' Peace", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Greek", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Athens", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Sparta", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He was honoured with the Order of the Republic of Guinea and Nigeria , second highest national honours of Grand Commander of the Order of the Niger ( GCON ) .", "tokens": ["He", "was", "honoured", "with", "the", "Order", "of", "the", "Republic", "of", "Guinea", "and", "Nigeria", ",", "second", "highest", "national", "honours", "of", "Grand", "Commander", "of", "the", "Order", "of", "the", "Niger", "(", "GCON", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12], "text": "Order of the Republic of Guinea and Nigeria"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26], "text": "Grand Commander of the Order of the Niger"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [28], "text": "GCON"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Order of the Republic of Guinea and Nigeria", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Grand Commander of the Order of the Niger", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "GCON", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The p53 protein functions as a transcription factor with a crucial role in orchestrating the cellular stress response .", "tokens": ["The", "p53", "protein", "functions", "as", "a", "transcription", "factor", "with", "a", "crucial", "role", "in", "orchestrating", "the", "cellular", "stress", "response", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "p53 protein"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "p53 protein", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "London Bridge station was opened on 14 December 1836 , making it the oldest London railway terminus that is still running .", "tokens": ["London", "Bridge", "station", "was", "opened", "on", "14", "December", "1836", ",", "making", "it", "the", "oldest", "London", "railway", "terminus", "that", "is", "still", "running", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "London Bridge station"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14], "text": "London"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "London Bridge station", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Michael Witheford of `` TimeOut Melbourne `` describes the album as being `` almost a concept record ; the soundscape of a drive over the West Gate Bridge towards the refineries and container docks and far beyond .", "tokens": ["Michael", "Witheford", "of", "``", "TimeOut", "Melbourne", "``", "describes", "the", "album", "as", "being", "``", "almost", "a", "concept", "record", ";", "the", "soundscape", "of", "a", "drive", "over", "the", "West", "Gate", "Bridge", "towards", "the", "refineries", "and", "container", "docks", "and", "far", "beyond", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Michael Witheford"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "TimeOut Melbourne"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [25, 26, 27], "text": "West Gate Bridge"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Michael Witheford", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "TimeOut Melbourne", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "West Gate Bridge", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Crews liked the aircraft , and generally rated them better than the Spey-equipped FGR.2s .", "tokens": ["Crews", "liked", "the", "aircraft", ",", "and", "generally", "rated", "them", "better", "than", "the", "Spey-equipped", "FGR.2s", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [12, 13], "text": "Spey-equipped FGR.2s"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Spey-equipped FGR.2s", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "South of 120th Street , the eastern side of Claremont Avenue features the heavily fortified backside of the Barnard College campus .", "tokens": ["South", "of", "120th", "Street", ",", "the", "eastern", "side", "of", "Claremont", "Avenue", "features", "the", "heavily", "fortified", "backside", "of", "the", "Barnard", "College", "campus", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [2, 3], "text": "120th Street"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Claremont Avenue"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "Barnard College"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "120th Street", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Claremont Avenue", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Barnard College", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Bintan Resorts is separated from the rest of Bintan by a barbed wire fence , and land access to the rest of the land is via a single security checkpoint ( Post 1 checkpoint ) .", "tokens": ["Bintan", "Resorts", "is", "separated", "from", "the", "rest", "of", "Bintan", "by", "a", "barbed", "wire", "fence", ",", "and", "land", "access", "to", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "land", "is", "via", "a", "single", "security", "checkpoint", "(", "Post", "1", "checkpoint", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Bintan Resorts"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Bintan"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bintan Resorts", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bintan", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Furthermore , because the playoff format was also changed to ensure exclusive intradivisional play for the first two rounds of the 2021 Stanley Cup playoffs , any postseason rematch between Dallas and Tampa Bay will take place no later than the second round , making this series the first Stanley Cup Finals since 1967 Stanley Cup Finals ( which preceded the 1967 NHL expansion ) for which a rematch in the following year 's Finals will be impossible due to League realignment .", "tokens": ["Furthermore", ",", "because", "the", "playoff", "format", "was", "also", "changed", "to", "ensure", "exclusive", "intradivisional", "play", "for", "the", "first", "two", "rounds", "of", "the", "2021", "Stanley", "Cup", "playoffs", ",", "any", "postseason", "rematch", "between", "Dallas", "and", "Tampa", "Bay", "will", "take", "place", "no", "later", "than", "the", "second", "round", ",", "making", "this", "series", "the", "first", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "since", "1967", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "(", "which", "preceded", "the", "1967", "NHL", "expansion", ")", "for", "which", "a", "rematch", "in", "the", "following", "year", "'s", "Finals", "will", "be", "impossible", "due", "to", "League", "realignment", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [30], "text": "Dallas"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [32, 33], "text": "Tampa Bay"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [49, 50], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [54, 55], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [62], "text": "NHL"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dallas", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tampa Bay", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NHL", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "She died after giving birth to a boy and told the Brahman about the real identity of the boy .", "tokens": ["She", "died", "after", "giving", "birth", "to", "a", "boy", "and", "told", "the", "Brahman", "about", "the", "real", "identity", "of", "the", "boy", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [11], "text": "Brahman"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Brahman", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The whole area where the Sports Center is located is the town 's most important entertainment area .", "tokens": ["The", "whole", "area", "where", "the", "Sports", "Center", "is", "located", "is", "the", "town", "'s", "most", "important", "entertainment", "area", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [5, 6], "text": "Sports Center"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sports Center", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Rivière represented the first constituency of Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly from 2002 to 2007 as a member of the Union for a Popular Movement .", "tokens": ["Rivière", "represented", "the", "first", "constituency", "of", "Alpes-Maritimes", "in", "the", "French", "National", "Assembly", "from", "2002", "to", "2007", "as", "a", "member", "of", "the", "Union", "for", "a", "Popular", "Movement", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Rivière"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11], "text": "Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [21, 22, 23, 24, 25], "text": "Union for a Popular Movement"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Rivière", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Union for a Popular Movement", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Faculty of Food Technology ( ) is a faculty of Latvia University of Life Sciences and Technologies founded in 1948 .", "tokens": ["Faculty", "of", "Food", "Technology", "(", ")", "is", "a", "faculty", "of", "Latvia", "University", "of", "Life", "Sciences", "and", "Technologies", "founded", "in", "1948", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1, 2, 3], "text": "Faculty of Food Technology"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "text": "Latvia University of Life Sciences and Technologies"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Faculty of Food Technology", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Latvia University of Life Sciences and Technologies", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He continued to contribute to liberal politics and published poetry and hymns .", "tokens": ["He", "continued", "to", "contribute", "to", "liberal", "politics", "and", "published", "poetry", "and", "hymns", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The Club later changed its name from College Barge Club to College Boat Club .", "tokens": ["The", "Club", "later", "changed", "its", "name", "from", "College", "Barge", "Club", "to", "College", "Boat", "Club", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [7, 8, 9], "text": "College Barge Club"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "College Boat Club"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "College Barge Club", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "College Boat Club", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 2012 , the Prosecco research team at I NRIA Paris-Rocquencourt developed an efficient method of extracting the secret key from several PKCS # 11 cryptographic devices , including the SecurID 800 .", "tokens": ["In", "2012", ",", "the", "Prosecco", "research", "team", "at", "I", "NRIA", "Paris-Rocquencourt", "developed", "an", "efficient", "method", "of", "extracting", "the", "secret", "key", "from", "several", "PKCS", "#", "11", "cryptographic", "devices", ",", "including", "the", "SecurID", "800", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [4], "text": "Prosecco"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "NRIA Paris-Rocquencourt"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [30, 31], "text": "SecurID 800"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Prosecco", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NRIA Paris-Rocquencourt", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "SecurID 800", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "William 's successful invasion of England with a Dutch fleet and army led to his accession to the English throne as William III of England jointly with his wife Mary II of England , James ' daughter .", "tokens": ["William", "'s", "successful", "invasion", "of", "England", "with", "a", "Dutch", "fleet", "and", "army", "led", "to", "his", "accession", "to", "the", "English", "throne", "as", "William", "III", "of", "England", "jointly", "with", "his", "wife", "Mary", "II", "of", "England", ",", "James", "'", "daughter", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "William"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [5], "text": "England"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [8], "text": "Dutch"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18], "text": "English"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [21, 22], "text": "William III"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [24], "text": "England"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [29, 30], "text": "Mary II"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [32], "text": "England"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [34], "text": "James"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "William", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dutch", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "English", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "William III", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mary II", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "England", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "James", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Construction of Tarbela Dam was carried out in three stages to meet the diversion requirements of the river .", "tokens": ["Construction", "of", "Tarbela", "Dam", "was", "carried", "out", "in", "three", "stages", "to", "meet", "the", "diversion", "requirements", "of", "the", "river", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [2, 3], "text": "Tarbela Dam"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Tarbela Dam", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Lead guitar was not played by Ace Frehley as he was not musically involved with the album and it was not played by Vinnie Vincent either ; it was played by Steve Farris , who would go on to be the lead guitarist of the 1980s pop rock group Mr. Mister .", "tokens": ["Lead", "guitar", "was", "not", "played", "by", "Ace", "Frehley", "as", "he", "was", "not", "musically", "involved", "with", "the", "album", "and", "it", "was", "not", "played", "by", "Vinnie", "Vincent", "either", ";", "it", "was", "played", "by", "Steve", "Farris", ",", "who", "would", "go", "on", "to", "be", "the", "lead", "guitarist", "of", "the", "1980s", "pop", "rock", "group", "Mr.", "Mister", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Ace Frehley"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [23, 24], "text": "Vinnie Vincent"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [31, 32], "text": "Steve Farris"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [49, 50], "text": "Mr. Mister"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Ace Frehley", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Vinnie Vincent", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Steve Farris", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mr. Mister", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He died in a plane crash in 2002 .", "tokens": ["He", "died", "in", "a", "plane", "crash", "in", "2002", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "The house he lived in on Coldwell Street is called Treves House .", "tokens": ["The", "house", "he", "lived", "in", "on", "Coldwell", "Street", "is", "called", "Treves", "House", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Coldwell Street"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Treves House"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Coldwell Street", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Treves House", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The development was devised by the Greek planner Constantinos Apostolou Doxiadis , who also designed Islamabad and Riyadh .", "tokens": ["The", "development", "was", "devised", "by", "the", "Greek", "planner", "Constantinos", "Apostolou", "Doxiadis", ",", "who", "also", "designed", "Islamabad", "and", "Riyadh", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [6], "text": "Greek"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [8, 9, 10], "text": "Constantinos Apostolou Doxiadis"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [15], "text": "Islamabad"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [17], "text": "Riyadh"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Greek", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Constantinos Apostolou Doxiadis", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Islamabad", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Riyadh", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The quarterfinals of the tournament will be held at campus sites , while the semifinals and final took place at Glenn Warner Soccer Facility in Annapolis , Maryland .", "tokens": ["The", "quarterfinals", "of", "the", "tournament", "will", "be", "held", "at", "campus", "sites", ",", "while", "the", "semifinals", "and", "final", "took", "place", "at", "Glenn", "Warner", "Soccer", "Facility", "in", "Annapolis", ",", "Maryland", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [20, 21, 22, 23], "text": "Glenn Warner Soccer Facility"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [25], "text": "Annapolis"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [27], "text": "Maryland"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Glenn Warner Soccer Facility", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Annapolis", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Maryland", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "275 creating a special oversight committee for the special protection of children from all forms of neglect , abuse , cruelty , exploitation , discrimination and other conditions prejudicial to their development .", "tokens": ["275", "creating", "a", "special", "oversight", "committee", "for", "the", "special", "protection", "of", "children", "from", "all", "forms", "of", "neglect", ",", "abuse", ",", "cruelty", ",", "exploitation", ",", "discrimination", "and", "other", "conditions", "prejudicial", "to", "their", "development", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "He watched the 1958 World Cup as a journalist and saw the Brazilian national football team 's football .", "tokens": ["He", "watched", "the", "1958", "World", "Cup", "as", "a", "journalist", "and", "saw", "the", "Brazilian", "national", "football", "team", "'s", "football", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "World Cup"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "Brazilian"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "World Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Brazilian", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Bottlenose dolphins live in captivity across the world , though exact numbers are hard to determine .", "tokens": ["Bottlenose", "dolphins", "live", "in", "captivity", "across", "the", "world", ",", "though", "exact", "numbers", "are", "hard", "to", "determine", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Both fights took place at featherweight .", "tokens": ["Both", "fights", "took", "place", "at", "featherweight", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Born in 1943 , Stedman attended the University of Canterbury , graduating with a BSc ( Hons ) in physics in 1965 .", "tokens": ["Born", "in", "1943", ",", "Stedman", "attended", "the", "University", "of", "Canterbury", ",", "graduating", "with", "a", "BSc", "(", "Hons", ")", "in", "physics", "in", "1965", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4], "text": "Stedman"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [7, 8, 9], "text": "University of Canterbury"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "text": "BSc ( Hons ) in physics"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other", "organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Stedman", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "University of Canterbury", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "BSc ( Hons ) in physics", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
