{"text": "Alexandros is best known today for the Venus de Milo ( Aphrodite of Milos ) at the Louvre Museum in Paris , France .", "tokens": ["Alexandros", "is", "best", "known", "today", "for", "the", "Venus", "de", "Milo", "(", "Aphrodite", "of", "Milos", ")", "at", "the", "Louvre", "Museum", "in", "Paris", ",", "France", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0], "text": "Alexandros"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [7, 8, 9], "text": "Venus de Milo"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Aphrodite of Milos"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Louvre Museum"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [20], "text": "Paris"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "France"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "art", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Alexandros", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Venus de Milo", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Aphrodite of Milos", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Louvre Museum", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Paris", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "France", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "On January 11 , 2012 , Bill Haslam endorsed Mitt Romney for the Republican nomination in the 2012 United States presidential election .", "tokens": ["On", "January", "11", ",", "2012", ",", "Bill", "Haslam", "endorsed", "Mitt", "Romney", "for", "the", "Republican", "nomination", "in", "the", "2012", "United", "States", "presidential", "election", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10], "text": "Bill Haslam endorsed Mitt Romney"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [13], "text": "Republican"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "United States"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bill Haslam endorsed Mitt Romney", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Republican", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "United States", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Rivière represented the first constituency of Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly from 2002 to 2007 as a member of the Union for a Popular Movement .", "tokens": ["Rivière", "represented", "the", "first", "constituency", "of", "Alpes-Maritimes", "in", "the", "French", "National", "Assembly", "from", "2002", "to", "2007", "as", "a", "member", "of", "the", "Union", "for", "a", "Popular", "Movement", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Rivière"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11], "text": "Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [21, 22, 23, 24, 25], "text": "Union for a Popular Movement"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Rivière", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Alpes-Maritimes in the French National Assembly", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Union for a Popular Movement", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The King-Emperor , George V , released him in 1920 as the result of a general amnesty order .", "tokens": ["The", "King-Emperor", ",", "George", "V", ",", "released", "him", "in", "1920", "as", "the", "result", "of", "a", "general", "amnesty", "order", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "George V"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "George V", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "3 Idiots is a Pakistani television series that airs on Aaj TV on Saturdays at 8 pm .", "tokens": ["3", "Idiots", "is", "a", "Pakistani", "television", "series", "that", "airs", "on", "Aaj", "TV", "on", "Saturdays", "at", "8", "pm", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "3 Idiots"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [4], "text": "Pakistani"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Aaj TV"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "3 Idiots", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Pakistani", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Aaj TV", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "As the first such body to be discovered , Ceres was given the designation 1 Ceres under the modern system of minor-planet designations .", "tokens": ["As", "the", "first", "such", "body", "to", "be", "discovered", ",", "Ceres", "was", "given", "the", "designation", "1", "Ceres", "under", "the", "modern", "system", "of", "minor-planet", "designations", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [9], "text": "Ceres"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [15], "text": "Ceres"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Ceres", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Ceres", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Gough Island was formally claimed in 1938 for Britain , during a visit by HMS `` Milford '' of the Royal Navy .", "tokens": ["Gough", "Island", "was", "formally", "claimed", "in", "1938", "for", "Britain", ",", "during", "a", "visit", "by", "HMS", "``", "Milford", "''", "of", "the", "Royal", "Navy", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Gough Island"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [8], "text": "Britain"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [14, 15, 16, 17], "text": "HMS `` Milford ''"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [20, 21], "text": "Royal Navy"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Gough Island", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Britain", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "HMS `` Milford ''", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Royal Navy", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "1 , 22 June 1895 to 1896 .", "tokens": ["1", ",", "22", "June", "1895", "to", "1896", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "London Bridge station was opened on 14 December 1836 , making it the oldest London railway terminus that is still running .", "tokens": ["London", "Bridge", "station", "was", "opened", "on", "14", "December", "1836", ",", "making", "it", "the", "oldest", "London", "railway", "terminus", "that", "is", "still", "running", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1, 2], "text": "London Bridge station"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14], "text": "London"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "London Bridge station", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "London", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
