{"text": "Alexandros is best known today for the Venus de Milo ( Aphrodite of Milos ) at the Louvre Museum in Paris , France .", "tokens": ["Alexandros", "is", "best", "known", "today", "for", "the", "Venus", "de", "Milo", "(", "Aphrodite", "of", "Milos", ")", "at", "the", "Louvre", "Museum", "in", "Paris", ",", "France", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [0], "text": "Alexandros"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [7, 8, 9], "text": "Venus de Milo"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Aphrodite of Milos"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [17, 18], "text": "Louvre Museum"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [20], "text": "Paris"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [22], "text": "France"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "art", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Alexandros", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Venus de Milo", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Aphrodite of Milos", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Louvre Museum", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Paris", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "France", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The character will be portrayed by Sharon Duncan-Brewster in the 2021 Denis Villeneuve film , `` Dune `` .", "tokens": ["The", "character", "will", "be", "portrayed", "by", "Sharon", "Duncan-Brewster", "in", "the", "2021", "Denis", "Villeneuve", "film", ",", "``", "Dune", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11, 12], "text": "Denis Villeneuve"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [16], "text": "Dune"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Denis Villeneuve", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dune", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Every five years the ARBA publishes a detailed guide entitled `` Standard of Perfection `` .", "tokens": ["Every", "five", "years", "the", "ARBA", "publishes", "a", "detailed", "guide", "entitled", "``", "Standard", "of", "Perfection", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [4], "text": "ARBA"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Standard of Perfection"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "ARBA", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Standard of Perfection", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He plays Chief Irvin Irving on Amazon Prime 's `` Bosch `` .", "tokens": ["He", "plays", "Chief", "Irvin", "Irving", "on", "Amazon", "Prime", "'s", "``", "Bosch", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [3, 4], "text": "Irvin Irving"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Amazon Prime"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [10], "text": "Bosch"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Irvin Irving", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Amazon Prime", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bosch", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "On May 8 , 2005 , the `` Bleed Like Me `` music video was playlisted by Fuse , and a week later by MTVU and VH1 .", "tokens": ["On", "May", "8", ",", "2005", ",", "the", "``", "Bleed", "Like", "Me", "``", "music", "video", "was", "playlisted", "by", "Fuse", ",", "and", "a", "week", "later", "by", "MTVU", "and", "VH1", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [8, 9, 10], "text": "Bleed Like Me"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [17], "text": "Fuse"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [24], "text": "MTVU"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [26], "text": "VH1"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Bleed Like Me", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Fuse", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "MTVU", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "VH1", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "D at the University of Hawaii at Manoa .", "tokens": ["D", "at", "the", "University", "of", "Hawaii", "at", "Manoa", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4, 5], "text": "University of Hawaii"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [7], "text": "Manoa"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "University of Hawaii", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Manoa", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Until 1928 there were no official RFB groups in Bavaria .", "tokens": ["Until", "1928", "there", "were", "no", "official", "RFB", "groups", "in", "Bavaria", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [6], "text": "RFB"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [9], "text": "Bavaria"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "RFB", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Bavaria", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "NESN has carried regional Atlantic Coast Conference college basketball games since Boston College joined the conference , including games distributed for national broadcast for and by Fox Sports Networks .", "tokens": ["NESN", "has", "carried", "regional", "Atlantic", "Coast", "Conference", "college", "basketball", "games", "since", "Boston", "College", "joined", "the", "conference", ",", "including", "games", "distributed", "for", "national", "broadcast", "for", "and", "by", "Fox", "Sports", "Networks", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [0], "text": "NESN"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [4, 5, 6], "text": "Atlantic Coast Conference"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [11, 12], "text": "Boston College"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [26, 27, 28], "text": "Fox Sports Networks"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "NESN", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Atlantic Coast Conference", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Boston College", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Fox Sports Networks", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Furthermore , because the playoff format was also changed to ensure exclusive intradivisional play for the first two rounds of the 2021 Stanley Cup playoffs , any postseason rematch between Dallas and Tampa Bay will take place no later than the second round , making this series the first Stanley Cup Finals since 1967 Stanley Cup Finals ( which preceded the 1967 NHL expansion ) for which a rematch in the following year 's Finals will be impossible due to League realignment .", "tokens": ["Furthermore", ",", "because", "the", "playoff", "format", "was", "also", "changed", "to", "ensure", "exclusive", "intradivisional", "play", "for", "the", "first", "two", "rounds", "of", "the", "2021", "Stanley", "Cup", "playoffs", ",", "any", "postseason", "rematch", "between", "Dallas", "and", "Tampa", "Bay", "will", "take", "place", "no", "later", "than", "the", "second", "round", ",", "making", "this", "series", "the", "first", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "since", "1967", "Stanley", "Cup", "Finals", "(", "which", "preceded", "the", "1967", "NHL", "expansion", ")", "for", "which", "a", "rematch", "in", "the", "following", "year", "'s", "Finals", "will", "be", "impossible", "due", "to", "League", "realignment", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [30], "text": "Dallas"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [32, 33], "text": "Tampa Bay"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [49, 50], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [54, 55], "text": "Stanley Cup"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [62], "text": "NHL"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dallas", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Tampa Bay", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Stanley Cup", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "NHL", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "On 25 April , Krukenberg was appointed by General Helmuth Weidling as the commander of ( Berlin ) Defence Sector C , which included the SS Division Nordland , whose previous commander Joachim Ziegler was relieved of his command the same day .", "tokens": ["On", "25", "April", ",", "Krukenberg", "was", "appointed", "by", "General", "Helmuth", "Weidling", "as", "the", "commander", "of", "(", "Berlin", ")", "Defence", "Sector", "C", ",", "which", "included", "the", "SS", "Division", "Nordland", ",", "whose", "previous", "commander", "Joachim", "Ziegler", "was", "relieved", "of", "his", "command", "the", "same", "day", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4], "text": "Krukenberg"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Helmuth Weidling"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [16], "text": "Berlin"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [18, 19, 20], "text": "Defence Sector C"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [25, 26, 27], "text": "SS Division Nordland"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [32, 33], "text": "Joachim Ziegler"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Krukenberg", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Helmuth Weidling", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Berlin", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Defence Sector C", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "SS Division Nordland", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Joachim Ziegler", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Jurist was launched as part of Operation Zipper , the overall British plan to liberate Malaya , including Singapore .", "tokens": ["Jurist", "was", "launched", "as", "part", "of", "Operation", "Zipper", ",", "the", "overall", "British", "plan", "to", "liberate", "Malaya", ",", "including", "Singapore", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [0], "text": "Jurist"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Operation Zipper"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [11], "text": "British"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "Malaya"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [18], "text": "Singapore"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Jurist", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Operation Zipper", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "British", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Malaya", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Singapore", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "After the Romanian Revolution of 1989 he joined the National Liberal Party , being appointed director of the `` Viitorul `` newspaper , the official daily of the party .", "tokens": ["After", "the", "Romanian", "Revolution", "of", "1989", "he", "joined", "the", "National", "Liberal", "Party", ",", "being", "appointed", "director", "of", "the", "``", "Viitorul", "``", "newspaper", ",", "the", "official", "daily", "of", "the", "party", "."], "entity": [{"type": "event", "offset": [2, 3], "text": "Romanian Revolution"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [9, 10, 11], "text": "National Liberal Party"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [19], "text": "Viitorul"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Romanian Revolution", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "National Liberal Party", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Viitorul", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Dadoo was banned from attending all gatherings and ordered to resign from the SAIC and the Defiance Campaign planning committee .", "tokens": ["Dadoo", "was", "banned", "from", "attending", "all", "gatherings", "and", "ordered", "to", "resign", "from", "the", "SAIC", "and", "the", "Defiance", "Campaign", "planning", "committee", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Dadoo"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [13], "text": "SAIC"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "Defiance Campaign"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "event", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Dadoo", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "SAIC", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Defiance Campaign", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "In 1986 the Communist Party of National Liberation , a secessionist splinter of the Galician Galician People 's Union , was expelled from the BNG for having supported the candidacy of Herri Batasuna during the Elections to the European Parliament European Parliament .", "tokens": ["In", "1986", "the", "Communist", "Party", "of", "National", "Liberation", ",", "a", "secessionist", "splinter", "of", "the", "Galician", "Galician", "People", "'s", "Union", ",", "was", "expelled", "from", "the", "BNG", "for", "having", "supported", "the", "candidacy", "of", "Herri", "Batasuna", "during", "the", "Elections", "to", "the", "European", "Parliament", "European", "Parliament", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [3, 4, 5, 6, 7], "text": "Communist Party of National Liberation"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [14], "text": "Galician"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [15, 16, 17, 18], "text": "Galician People 's Union"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [24], "text": "BNG"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [31, 32], "text": "Herri Batasuna"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [35, 36, 37, 38, 39], "text": "Elections to the European Parliament"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [40], "text": "European"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["event", "organization", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Communist Party of National Liberation", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Galician", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Galician People 's Union", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "BNG", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Herri Batasuna", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Elections to the European Parliament", "label": "event", "asoc": []}, {"span": "European", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Mil Mi-58 was a projected twin-turbine passenger helicopter based on the Mil Mi-28 first announced at the 1995 Paris Air Show .", "tokens": ["The", "Mil", "Mi-58", "was", "a", "projected", "twin-turbine", "passenger", "helicopter", "based", "on", "the", "Mil", "Mi-28", "first", "announced", "at", "the", "1995", "Paris", "Air", "Show", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "Mil Mi-58"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [12, 13], "text": "Mil Mi-28"}, {"type": "event", "offset": [18, 19, 20, 21], "text": "1995 Paris Air Show"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "event"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Mil Mi-58", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Mil Mi-28", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "1995 Paris Air Show", "label": "event", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "However , Buddah head Neil Bogart liked the demo enough that he released the record `` as is '' , with Levine 's vocals intact and no input at all from the touring version of the Ohio Express .", "tokens": ["However", ",", "Buddah", "head", "Neil", "Bogart", "liked", "the", "demo", "enough", "that", "he", "released", "the", "record", "``", "as", "is", "''", ",", "with", "Levine", "'s", "vocals", "intact", "and", "no", "input", "at", "all", "from", "the", "touring", "version", "of", "the", "Ohio", "Express", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "Neil Bogart"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [21], "text": "Levine"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [36, 37], "text": "Ohio Express"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Neil Bogart", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Levine", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Ohio Express", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "A coup d'état by Nikita Khrushchev , with help from Marshal of the Soviet Union Georgy Zhukov in June 1953 , removed Beria from power .", "tokens": ["A", "coup", "d'état", "by", "Nikita", "Khrushchev", ",", "with", "help", "from", "Marshal", "of", "the", "Soviet", "Union", "Georgy", "Zhukov", "in", "June", "1953", ",", "removed", "Beria", "from", "power", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [4, 5], "text": "Nikita Khrushchev"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [15, 16], "text": "Georgy Zhukov"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [22], "text": "Beria"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Nikita Khrushchev", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Georgy Zhukov", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Beria", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The character will be portrayed by Sharon Duncan-Brewster in the 2021 Denis Villeneuve film , `` Dune `` .", "tokens": ["The", "character", "will", "be", "portrayed", "by", "Sharon", "Duncan-Brewster", "in", "the", "2021", "Denis", "Villeneuve", "film", ",", "``", "Dune", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11, 12], "text": "Denis Villeneuve"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [16], "text": "Dune"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sharon Duncan-Brewster", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Denis Villeneuve", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Dune", "label": "art", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Kiev pocket was sealed when panzers of the 3 .", "tokens": ["The", "Kiev", "pocket", "was", "sealed", "when", "panzers", "of", "the", "3", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [1], "text": "Kiev"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Kiev", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "But in 2016 , the three-tome `` Animation - A World History `` was published by CRC Press ( Italian version `` '' Animazione - una storia globale `` , '' Milan , Utet , 2017 ) .", "tokens": ["But", "in", "2016", ",", "the", "three-tome", "``", "Animation", "-", "A", "World", "History", "``", "was", "published", "by", "CRC", "Press", "(", "Italian", "version", "``", "''", "Animazione", "-", "una", "storia", "globale", "``", ",", "''", "Milan", ",", "Utet", ",", "2017", ")", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [7, 8, 9, 10, 11], "text": "Animation - A World History"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [16, 17], "text": "CRC Press"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [18, 19], "text": "( Italian"}, {"type": "art", "offset": [23, 24, 25, 26, 27], "text": "Animazione - una storia globale"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [31], "text": "Milan"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [33], "text": "Utet"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "organization", "location", "other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Animation - A World History", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "CRC Press", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "( Italian", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Animazione - una storia globale", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Milan", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Utet", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "It is considered to be one of the holiest Islamic sites in Egypt .", "tokens": ["It", "is", "considered", "to", "be", "one", "of", "the", "holiest", "Islamic", "sites", "in", "Egypt", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [9], "text": "Islamic"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12], "text": "Egypt"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Islamic", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Egypt", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The 90,000 Pakistani troops under Niazi 's command surrendered to Gen Aurora as prisoners of war .", "tokens": ["The", "90,000", "Pakistani", "troops", "under", "Niazi", "'s", "command", "surrendered", "to", "Gen", "Aurora", "as", "prisoners", "of", "war", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [2], "text": "Pakistani"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [5], "text": "Niazi"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Gen Aurora"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Pakistani", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Niazi", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Gen Aurora", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "12 Corazones ( , `` 12 Hearts '' ) is a Spanish -language dating game show produced in the United States for the television network Telemundo since January 2005 , based on its namesake Argentine TV show format The show is filmed in Los Angeles and revolves around the twelve Zodiac signs that identify each contestant .", "tokens": ["12", "Corazones", "(", ",", "``", "12", "Hearts", "''", ")", "is", "a", "Spanish", "-language", "dating", "game", "show", "produced", "in", "the", "United", "States", "for", "the", "television", "network", "Telemundo", "since", "January", "2005", ",", "based", "on", "its", "namesake", "Argentine", "TV", "show", "format", "The", "show", "is", "filmed", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "and", "revolves", "around", "the", "twelve", "Zodiac", "signs", "that", "identify", "each", "contestant", "."], "entity": [{"type": "art", "offset": [1], "text": "Corazones"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [11], "text": "Spanish"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "United States"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [34, 35], "text": "Argentine TV"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [43, 44], "text": "Los Angeles"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [50], "text": "Zodiac"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["art", "other", "organization", "person", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Corazones", "label": "art", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Spanish", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "United States", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Argentine TV", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Los Angeles", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Zodiac", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Amphiphysin is a brain-enriched protein with an N-terminal lipid interaction , dimerisation and membrane bending BAR domain , a middle clathrin and adaptor binding domain and a C-terminal SH3 domain .", "tokens": ["Amphiphysin", "is", "a", "brain-enriched", "protein", "with", "an", "N-terminal", "lipid", "interaction", ",", "dimerisation", "and", "membrane", "bending", "BAR", "domain", ",", "a", "middle", "clathrin", "and", "adaptor", "binding", "domain", "and", "a", "C-terminal", "SH3", "domain", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [0], "text": "Amphiphysin"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "N-terminal lipid"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [15], "text": "BAR"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [27, 28, 29], "text": "C-terminal SH3 domain"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Amphiphysin", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "N-terminal lipid", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "BAR", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "C-terminal SH3 domain", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The Yellowstone Park bison herd was the last free-ranging bison herd in the United States and the only place where they did not go locally extinct , so they have become at least part of the foundation stock for many other herds , including the Wind Cave bison herd .", "tokens": ["The", "Yellowstone", "Park", "bison", "herd", "was", "the", "last", "free-ranging", "bison", "herd", "in", "the", "United", "States", "and", "the", "only", "place", "where", "they", "did", "not", "go", "locally", "extinct", ",", "so", "they", "have", "become", "at", "least", "part", "of", "the", "foundation", "stock", "for", "many", "other", "herds", ",", "including", "the", "Wind", "Cave", "bison", "herd", "."], "entity": [{"type": "location", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "Yellowstone Park"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [3], "text": "bison"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [9], "text": "bison"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "United States"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [45, 46], "text": "Wind Cave"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [47], "text": "bison"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["other", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Yellowstone Park", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "bison", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "bison", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "United States", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Wind Cave", "label": "location", "asoc": []}, {"span": "bison", "label": "other", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "After residency in Pediatrics at Hokkaido University Hospital , he worked as a pediatrician in Japan for several years .", "tokens": ["After", "residency", "in", "Pediatrics", "at", "Hokkaido", "University", "Hospital", ",", "he", "worked", "as", "a", "pediatrician", "in", "Japan", "for", "several", "years", "."], "entity": [{"type": "other", "offset": [3], "text": "Pediatrics"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [5, 6, 7], "text": "Hokkaido University Hospital"}, {"type": "other", "offset": [13], "text": "pediatrician"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15], "text": "Japan"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "other", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Pediatrics", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hokkaido University Hospital", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "pediatrician", "label": "other", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Japan", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "`` Play US `` gave it three stars out of five and said , `` Hardcore RPG fans should add another star to the score and reserve a copy immediately . ''", "tokens": ["``", "Play", "US", "``", "gave", "it", "three", "stars", "out", "of", "five", "and", "said", ",", "``", "Hardcore", "RPG", "fans", "should", "add", "another", "star", "to", "the", "score", "and", "reserve", "a", "copy", "immediately", ".", "''"], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [1, 2], "text": "Play US"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [15, 16], "text": "Hardcore RPG"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Play US", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hardcore RPG", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "It is the sequel to the Sega Dreamcast game `` Airforce Delta `` .", "tokens": ["It", "is", "the", "sequel", "to", "the", "Sega", "Dreamcast", "game", "``", "Airforce", "Delta", "``", "."], "entity": [{"type": "organization", "offset": [6, 7], "text": "Sega Dreamcast"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [10, 11], "text": "Airforce Delta"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["organization", "product"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Sega Dreamcast", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Airforce Delta", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Accordingly , R101 changed course : the new course would take it directly over the Beauvais Ridge , an area notorious for turbulent wind conditions .", "tokens": ["Accordingly", ",", "R101", "changed", "course", ":", "the", "new", "course", "would", "take", "it", "directly", "over", "the", "Beauvais", "Ridge", ",", "an", "area", "notorious", "for", "turbulent", "wind", "conditions", "."], "entity": [{"type": "product", "offset": [2], "text": "R101"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [15, 16], "text": "Beauvais Ridge"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "R101", "label": "product", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Beauvais Ridge", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Although the game features his name , Tom Clancy had little to no involvement in the development of any of the Splinter Cell games .", "tokens": ["Although", "the", "game", "features", "his", "name", ",", "Tom", "Clancy", "had", "little", "to", "no", "involvement", "in", "the", "development", "of", "any", "of", "the", "Splinter", "Cell", "games", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [7, 8], "text": "Tom Clancy"}, {"type": "product", "offset": [21, 22], "text": "Splinter Cell"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["product", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Tom Clancy", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Splinter Cell", "label": "product", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "The law proposed to establish a corporativist state .", "tokens": ["The", "law", "proposed", "to", "establish", "a", "corporativist", "state", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Local people raised money to construct it in 1905 and reconstructed it many times afterwards .", "tokens": ["Local", "people", "raised", "money", "to", "construct", "it", "in", "1905", "and", "reconstructed", "it", "many", "times", "afterwards", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Paul International airport .", "tokens": ["Paul", "International", "airport", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "His feast day is 19 May .", "tokens": ["His", "feast", "day", "is", "19", "May", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "After considering several options , they try to make a short film .", "tokens": ["After", "considering", "several", "options", ",", "they", "try", "to", "make", "a", "short", "film", "."], "entity": [], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": [], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": []}
{"text": "Little Rissington became the largest military contingency hospital in Europe .", "tokens": ["Little", "Rissington", "became", "the", "largest", "military", "contingency", "hospital", "in", "Europe", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [0, 1], "text": "Little Rissington"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [9], "text": "Europe"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Little Rissington", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Europe", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Formerly known as the Communiplex , it is home to the WHL 's Prince Albert Raiders and the Prince Albert Mintos .", "tokens": ["Formerly", "known", "as", "the", "Communiplex", ",", "it", "is", "home", "to", "the", "WHL", "'s", "Prince", "Albert", "Raiders", "and", "the", "Prince", "Albert", "Mintos", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [4], "text": "Communiplex"}, {"type": "organization", "offset": [11], "text": "WHL"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [14, 15], "text": "Albert Raiders"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [19, 20], "text": "Albert Mintos"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "organization", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Communiplex", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "WHL", "label": "organization", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Albert Raiders", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Albert Mintos", "label": "person", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Plimpton died of complications resulting from pneumonia , at Huntington Hospital on Long Island , on July 30 , 1983 .", "tokens": ["Plimpton", "died", "of", "complications", "resulting", "from", "pneumonia", ",", "at", "Huntington", "Hospital", "on", "Long", "Island", ",", "on", "July", "30", ",", "1983", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [0], "text": "Plimpton"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [9, 10], "text": "Huntington Hospital"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [12, 13], "text": "Long Island"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Plimpton", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Huntington Hospital", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Long Island", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "Among the buildings of a civil nature can be mentioned the Hacienda Sin Nombre ( With No Name ) , the Hacienda del Burro de Oro ( Golden Donkey ) and the nursing home of San José .", "tokens": ["Among", "the", "buildings", "of", "a", "civil", "nature", "can", "be", "mentioned", "the", "Hacienda", "Sin", "Nombre", "(", "With", "No", "Name", ")", ",", "the", "Hacienda", "del", "Burro", "de", "Oro", "(", "Golden", "Donkey", ")", "and", "the", "nursing", "home", "of", "San", "José", "."], "entity": [{"type": "building", "offset": [11, 12, 13], "text": "Hacienda Sin Nombre"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [21, 22, 23, 24, 25], "text": "Hacienda del Burro de Oro"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [27, 28], "text": "Golden Donkey"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [35, 36], "text": "San José"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Hacienda Sin Nombre", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Hacienda del Burro de Oro", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Golden Donkey", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "San José", "label": "building", "asoc": []}]}
{"text": "He was survived by his wife , Irma , and his brother , Sam Steiner , who was a manager at the Carnegie Deli at the time of Leo 's death and another brother Robert , a Stock Broker in Lakewood , NJ .", "tokens": ["He", "was", "survived", "by", "his", "wife", ",", "Irma", ",", "and", "his", "brother", ",", "Sam", "Steiner", ",", "who", "was", "a", "manager", "at", "the", "Carnegie", "Deli", "at", "the", "time", "of", "Leo", "'s", "death", "and", "another", "brother", "Robert", ",", "a", "Stock", "Broker", "in", "Lakewood", ",", "NJ", "."], "entity": [{"type": "person", "offset": [7], "text": "Irma"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [13, 14], "text": "Sam Steiner"}, {"type": "building", "offset": [22, 23], "text": "Carnegie Deli"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [28], "text": "Leo"}, {"type": "person", "offset": [34], "text": "Robert"}, {"type": "location", "offset": [40, 41, 42], "text": "Lakewood , NJ"}], "relation": [], "event": [], "spot": ["building", "location", "person"], "asoc": [], "spot_asoc": [{"span": "Irma", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Sam Steiner", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Carnegie Deli", "label": "building", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Leo", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Robert", "label": "person", "asoc": []}, {"span": "Lakewood , NJ", "label": "location", "asoc": []}]}
